Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records Addendum WAG.124.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: The Contract Correspondence of the Printing, Publishing and Media Workers Sector (PPMWS) Section, 1986
  - Subseries VIII:B: Typographical Union, 1986
    - Local 586: Greeley, CO, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 36)
    - Local 589: Santa Cruz, CA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 37)
    - Local 590: Gary, IN, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 38)
    - Local 593: Brainerd, MN, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 39)
    - Local 601: Warren, OH, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 40)
    - Local 613: Enid, OK, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 41)
    - Local 614: Yakima, WA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 42)
    - Local 620: Norristown, PA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 43)
    - Local 623: Fitchburg, MA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 44)
    - Local 627: Moose Jaw, SK-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 45)
    - Local 630: St. Cloud, MN, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 46)
    - Local 636: Moncton, NB-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 47)
    - Local 642: Hackensack, NJ, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 48)
    - Local 643: Waterville, MA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 49)
    - Local 644: Waldo, ME, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 50)
    - Local 649: Shamokin, PA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 51)
    - Local 650: Coast Valleys, CA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 52)
    - Local 651: Monterey Bay Area, CA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 53)
    - Local 657: Regina, SK-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 54)
    - Local 660: Tallahassee, FL, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 55)
    - Local 663: Print Media Union, SK-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 56)
    - Local 664: Fredericton, NB-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 57)
    - Local 667: Chico, CA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 58)
    - Local 668: Greenburg/Jeannette, PA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 59)
    - Local 679: Central Connecticut, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 60)
    - Local 705: Prince Albert, SK-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 61)
    - Local 709: West Palm Beach, FL, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 62)
    - Local 710: Sheboygan, WI, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 63)
    - Local 714: Laurel, MD, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 64)
    - Local 715: Pottstown, PA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 65)
    - Local 723: Kalispell, MT, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 66)
    - Local 727: Hibbing/Virginia, MN, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 67)
    - Local 713: Grand Island, NE, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 68)
    - Local 733: Kittanning, PA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 69)
    - Local 736: International Falls, MN, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 70)
    - Local 743: Middletown, CT, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 71)
    - Local 746: Sault Ste. Marie, ON-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 72)
    - Local 764: Havre, MT, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 73)
    - Local 769: Plattsburg, NY, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 74)
    - Local 771: Dothan, AL, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 75)
    - Local 787: Ashland, KY, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 76)
    - Local 792: Mankato, MN, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 77)
    - Local 807: Oelwein, IA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 78)
    - Local 809: Laconia, NH, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 79)
    - Local 813: Lebanon, PA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 80)
    - Local 819: Rochester, NY, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 81)
    - Local 821: Biloxi/Gulfport, MS, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 82)
    - Local 823: Anchorage, AK, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 83)
    - Local 824: Albert Lea/ Austin, MN, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 84)
    - Local 827: Marshfield, OR, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 85)
    - Local 832: Lafayette, LA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 86)
    - Local 833: Torrington, CT, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 87)
    - Local 837: Sarina, ON-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 88)
    - Local 838: Alpena, MI, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 89)
    - Local 846: Sudbury, ON-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 90)
    - Local 848: Madera, CA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 91)
    - Local 859: Cornwall, ON-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 92)
    - Local 867: Pembroke, ON-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 93)
    - Local 868: Price George, BC-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 94)
    - Local 873: Barrie, ON-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 95)
    - Local 874: Gadsden, AL, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 96)
    - Local 879: Iron Mountain, MI, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 97)
    - Local 892: Daytona, FL, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 98)
    - Local 893: Charles City, IA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 99)
    - Local 909: Ventura, CA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 100)
    - Local 915: Long Island City, NY, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 101)
    - Local 927: Welland, ON-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 102)
    - Local 933: Las Vegas, NV, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 103)
    - Local 935: Dixon, IL, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 104)
    - Local 943: East Stroudsburg, PA, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 105)
    - Local 963: Charlottetown, P.E.I.-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 106)
    - Local 965: Progressive Schedule Employees Association, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 107)
    - Local 969: Oshawa, ON-Canada, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 108)
- Series IX: Files of the Public Affairs Section, 1983-1991.
  - American Family Celebration (I), 1988 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - American Family Celebration (II), 1988 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - American Family Celebration (III), 1988 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph (AT&T): Credit Card Release, Jan 23, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - AT&T: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission/women Settlement, Jul 17, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - AT&T: Flunking Efficiency Test, Feb 28, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - AT&T/National Cash Register (NCR) Merger, May 7, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - AT&T/NCR News Conference-Dayton, OH, Oct 28, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - AT&T: National Picketing, Jan 24, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - AT&T: Transfer of Union Jobs to NCR, Sep 5, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - AT&T: Workers Blamed on Service Disruption, Sep 19, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 11)
  - Anti-bugging Campaign: Don't Bug Me, 1987-1988 (Box 164, Folder 12)
  - Austin Cable Boycott, Nov 14, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 13)
  - Bahr Address to Workers at Council for Adult and Experiential Learning (CAEL) Training Conference, Nov 4, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Bahr Letters in Support of Made in USA, Apr 1, 1990 (Box 164, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining (I), 1986 (Box 164, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining (II), 1986 (Box 164, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining (I), 1989 (Box 164, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining (II), 1989 (Box 164, Folder 19)
  - Bargaining: AT&T, 1986-1989 (Box 164, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining: Bell System, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining: General Telephone Company (GTE), 1989 (Box 164, Folder 22)
  - Bargaining: Regional Bell Operating Companies (RBOC), 1986 (Box 164, Folder 23)
  - Bell Atlantic Pension Negotiation, Oct 15, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 24)
  - Bell System: Support for Manufacturing Legislation, Jan 18, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 25)
  - Common Interest Forum, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 26)
  - Communications School: Organizers Binder, 1988 (Box 164, Folder 27)
  - Communications School: Participants Binder, 1988 (Box 164, Folder 28)
  - Computer Operator Telephone News Conference, Mar 22, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 29)
  - Convention Announcement, Jun 17, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 30)
  - Convention Records (I), 1986 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Convention Records (II), 1986 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Convention Records (I), 1987 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Convention Records (II), 1987 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Convention Records, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Convention Records: Speeches of Potential Democratic Presidential Candidates, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - CAEL conference on Training and Education, Oct 31, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Federal Communication Commission (FCC) Report on AT&T, Nov 8, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Student Organizing, Oct 16, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Gulf War Opposition, Jan 9, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - High Tech Health Hazards: Semi-Conductor Industry, Mar 4, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - International Business Machines (IBM), 1986-1987 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Jobs with Justice (JwJ): Healthcare Action Week Teleconference, May 1, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - JwJ: Healthcare Teleconference at Press Club, May 1, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - JwJ: Health Insurance Trade Association-Administrative Waste, Jun 3, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Conference, Mar 18, 1991-Mar 21, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - Monitoring Binder, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, Jan 1989-Jul 1989 (Box 165, Folder 18)
  - News Clippings (I), Aug 1989 (Box 165, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings (II), Aug 1989 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings (I), Sep 1989 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings (II), Sep 1989 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings (I), Oct 1989 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings (II), Oct 1989 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings (I), Nov 1989 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings (II), Nov 1989 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings (I), Dec 1989 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings (II), Dec 1989 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings (I), Jan 1990 (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings (II), Jan 1990 (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, Feb 1990-Mar 1990 (Box 166, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, Aug 1991 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings (I), Sep 1991 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings (II), Sep 1991 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings (III), Sep 1991 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings (I), Oct 1991 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings (II), Oct 1991 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings (III), Oct 1991 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, Nov 1991 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, Dec 1991 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings: Bell South-Bargaining, 1989 (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings: US West-Bargaining, 1989 (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - News: Daily Summaries (I), Jan 1989 (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - News: Daily Summaries (II), Jan 1989 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - News: Daily Summaries (I), Feb 1989 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - News: Daily Summaries (II), Feb 1989 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - News: Daily Summaries (I), Mar 1989 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - News: Daily Summaries (II), Mar 1989 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - News: Daily Summaries (I), Apr 1989 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - News: Daily Summaries (II), Apr 1989 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - News: Daily Summaries, May 1989 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - News: Daily Summaries (I), Jun 1989 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - News: Daily Summaries (II), Jun 1989 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Jul 1989 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - News: Daily Summaries (I), Aug 1989 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - News: Daily Summaries (II), Aug 1989 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - News: Daily Summaries (III), Aug 1989 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Sep 1989 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Oct 1989 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Nov 1989 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Dec 1989 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Jan 1990 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Feb 1990 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Mar 1990 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Apr 1990-May 1990 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Jun 1990-Jul 1990 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Nov 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - News: Daily Summaries, Jan 1991-Jun 1991 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Northern Telecom: Message from Toronto Unions, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Northern Telecom: Union Strategy Meeting, Oct 21, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Northern Telecom: Workplace Privacy-District Court Defeat, Apr 24, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Press Release: Advisory-Electronic Monitoring, VDT, Oct 3, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - Press Release: AT&T Bid for NCR, Dec 19, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - Press Release: AT&T Layoffs, Jan 1990 (Box 170, Folder 15)
  - Press Release: AT&T Reaching Out to Touch Managers and Stockholders, Mar 28, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 16)
  - Press Release: AT&T Taking Service Out of Network Service, Jul 10, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 17)
  - Press Release: CWA-Canada Enter Alliance-First of its Kind, Jun 11, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 18)
  - Press Release: CWA Demonstration Against AT&T, Feb 15, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 19)
  - Press Release: CWA Files Charges Against Western Union, Aug 13, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 20)
  - Press Release: CWA Legislative-Political Conference, Mar 21, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 21)
  - Press Release: CWA Opposes AT&T Bid for NCR, Dec 4, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 22)
  - Press Release: CWA Sues District of Columbia for Taxi Drivers, Sep 6, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 23)
  - Press Release: CWA to Demonstrate at National Council of Social Workers Rally to Support Contract Talks, Mar 26, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 24)
  - Press Release: Contel Workers Set Strike for 1/27/90, Jan 26, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 25)
  - Press Release: Demonstration at US Sprint Headquarters-Kansas City, MO, Oct 15, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 26)
  - Press Release: Flexcare Flyer, Jun 23, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 27)
  - Press Release: Ft. Wayne Radio Stations Veto Union Ads, Dec 10, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 28)
  - Press Release: Healthcare: Canadian v. US in topic at Labor Forum, Mar 28, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 29)
  - Press Release: Indiana University Poverty Pay Level, Jul 1990 (Box 170, Folder 30)
  - Press Release: JwJ Audio News Conference, Jul 11, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 31)
  - Press Release: JwJ Rally-Columbia State Fairgrounds, SC, Aug 16, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 32)
  - Press Release: JwJ Healthcare Action Day- Oct 3, 1990, Sep 28, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 33)
  - Press Release: JwJ Teleconference, Jul 24, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 34)
  - Press Release: New York Telephone and New England Telephone and Telegraph (NYNEX) Settlement Briefing, Sep 17, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 35)
  - Press Release: Northern Telecom Sued by CWA, Oct 5, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 36)
  - Press Release: Simon Introduces Privacy for Consumers and Workers Act, Feb 23, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 37)
  - Press Release: Statement by Local 4211 President Gayle Gray, Apr 9, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 38)
  - Press Release: Statement on AT&T Layoffs-Dina Beaumont, Dec 11, 1989 (Box 170, Folder 39)
  - Press Release: Taylor Made Negotiating, Jan 1990 (Box 170, Folder 40)
  - Press Release: Unfair Labor Charges Against United Telecom-Bristol, TN, Oct 23, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 41)
  - Press Release: Unions Protest AT&T Hypocrisy; Picket Shareholder Meeting, Apr 1990 (Box 170, Folder 42)
  - Press Release: United Healthcare Action-Bristol, TN, Dec 13, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 43)
  - Press Release: United Telephone-Dalles, OR, Nov 19, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 44)
  - Press Release: United Telephone-Fayetteville, NC, Nov 19, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 45)
  - Press Release: Vote NO to Robots, Jul 5, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 46)
  - Press Release: We Make a Difference, May 1, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 47)
  - Press Release: Western Union Agreement Reached, Aug 15, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 48)
  - Press Release: Western Union Pickets DC, Aug 14, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 49)
  - Press Release: Western Union Rally-New York, NY, Aug 8, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 50)
  - Press Release: Western Union Rally-Reno, NV, Aug 9, 1990 (Box 170, Folder 51)
  - Public Relations: 99 Ways to Say He/She Said, Undated (Box 170, Folder 52)
  - Public Relations: Agendas, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 53)
  - Public Relations: District PR Coordinators Leadership Seminar (Draft), Mar 7, 1983-Mar 8, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 54)
  - Public Relations: District PR Coordinators Leadership Seminar, Mar 7, 1983-Mar 8, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 55)
  - Public Relations: Fact Sheet, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 56)
  - Public Relations: Handouts, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 57)
  - Public Relations: How to Plan a News Conference, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 58)
  - Public Relations: Key Points in Writing a News Release, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 59)
  - Public Relations: Local Committee Training, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 60)
  - Public Relations: Media Relations Tips, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 61)
  - Public Relations: Media Workshop Evaluations, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 62)
  - Public Relations: Newsletter Contest, 1989 (Box 170, Folder 63)
  - Public Relations: News Media Card File, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 64)
  - Public Relations: Pitching the Story, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 65)
  - Public Relations: Promotional Flyer, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 66)
  - Public Relations: Scenarios, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 67)
  - Public Relations: Standard of Living, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 68)
  - Public Relations: Successful Media Relations During Bargaining, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 69)
  - Public Relations: Tips on Videotaping Union Events, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 70)
  - Public Relations: Training Materials Checklist, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 71)
  - Public Relations: Union Message Out Through the News Media, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 72)
  - RBOC Media Relations Kit, 1986 (Box 170, Folder 73)
  - Senate Sub-Committee on Workplace Privacy, Sep 24, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 74)
  - United Service Organization (USO)/CWA I'm Okay Program (Gulf War), Feb 14, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 75)
  - Unity: Collective Bargaining Partnership, 1988-1989 (Box 170, Folder 76)
  - Video Display Terminals (VDT's): OSHA Emergency Action, Jul 3, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 77)
  - Women's Wages: A Key to Preserving Middle Income Jobs, Nov 1986 (Box 170, Folder 78)
- Series X: Files of the Public and Health-Care Workers Section, 1986-1995.
  - Advisory Committee Meeting, Dec 17, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Agency Shop, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organization (AFL-CIO): Community Services Conference, Jun 15, 1992-Jun 18, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO: Community Services Conference, Jul 18, 1993-Jul 21, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Convention, Oct 23, 1995-Oct 26, 1995 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting, Feb 18, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO: National Safety and Health Conference, Dec 4, 1994-Dec 7, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO Public Employee Department: Executive Council Meeting, Feb 15, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute (APRI) Board Meeting, Jan 21, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - APRI Board Meeting, Feb 7, 1995 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - APRI Conference, Jun 9, 1993-Jun 12, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - APRI Conference, Jun 9, 1994-Jun 11, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - APRI Conference, Jun 28, 1995-Jul 11, 1995 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - APRI Executive Board Meeting, Jan 6, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - APRI National Board Meeting, Feb 7, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 15)
  - APRI National Education Conference, Jun 25, 1992-Jun 28, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining Contracts, Oct 25, 1992-Oct 30, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 17)
  - Bills Approved for Payment, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 18)
  - Bills Approved for Payment, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 19)
  - Bills Approved for Payment, 1989 (Box 171, Folder 20)
  - Bills Approved for Payment, 1990 (Box 171, Folder 21)
  - Bills Approved for Payment, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 22)
  - Bills Approved for Payment, Jan 1992-Jun 1992 (Box 171, Folder 23)
  - Bills Approved for Payment, Jul 1992-Dec 1992 (Box 171, Folder 24)
  - Campaign for New Priorities: Steering Committee, May 8, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 25)
  - Campaign for Quality Care Meeting, Feb 25, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 26)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Convention, May 21, 1992-May 25, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 27)
  - CBTU Convention, May 27, 1993-May 31, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 28)
  - CBTU Convention, May 25, 1994-May 30, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 29)
  - CBTU Convention, May 25, 1995-May 29, 1995 (Box 171, Folder 30)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW) Convention, Oct 5, 1991-Oct 7, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 31)
  - CWA Convention, 1989 (Box 171, Folder 32)
  - CWA Convention, 1990 (Box 171, Folder 33)
  - CWA Convention, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 34)
  - CWA Convention, 1992 (Box 171, Folder 35)
  - CWA Convention, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 36)
  - CWA Convention, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 37)
  - CWA Minority Caucus, Jul 25, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 38)
  - CWA Minority Caucus, Jun 9, 1994-Jun 11, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1988-Feb 1988 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1988-Apr 1988 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, May 1988-Jul 1988 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1989-Mar 1989 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1989-Jun 1989 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1989-Sep 1989 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1990-Feb 1990 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1990 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1990-May 1990 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1990-Aug 1990 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1991-Apr 1991 (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, May 1991-Sep 1991 (Box 172, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 172, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1992-Mar 1992 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1992 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, May 1992 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1992 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1992-Aug 1992 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1992-Oct 1992 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1992-Dec 1992 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1993-Feb 1993 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1993-Apr 1993 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, May 1993-Jun 1993 (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1993-Sep 1993 (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1994-Feb 1994 (Box 173, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1994 (Box 173, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1994 (Box 173, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, May 1994-Jul 1994 (Box 173, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 173, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1995-Apr 1995 (Box 173, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, May 1995 (Box 173, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1995-Jul 1995 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Aug 1995-Sep 1995 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Oct 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention, Jul 12, 1992-Jul 16, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Department of Professional Employees Convention, Oct 20, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - District 1 Conference, Nov 12, 1991-Nov 15, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - District 1 Conference, Oct 12, 1993-Oct 15, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - District 1 Conference, Oct 16, 1994-Oct 19, 1994 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - District 1 Health Care Conference, Feb 6, 1995-Feb 7, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - District 1 Health Care Conference, Apr 26, 1994 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - District 1 Health Care Locals Meeting, Jun 22, 1993-Jun 23, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - District 1 Health Care Symposium, Mar 23, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - District 1 Leadership Conference, Nov 15, 1992-Nov 18, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - District 1 Leadership Conference, Sep 26, 1995-Sep 29, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 14)
  - District 1 Minority Caucus, Apr 28, 1995-Apr 30, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 15)
  - District 3 Equity Conference, Apr 15, 1993-Apr 18, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 16)
  - District 3 Meeting, Apr 14, 1991-Apr 17, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - District 3 Meeting, Dec 13, 1991-Dec 15, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 18)
  - District 3 Meeting, Jun 14, 1993-Jun 16, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 19)
  - District 3 Meeting, Apr 3, 1993-Apr 6, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 20)
  - District 3 Meeting, Mar 19, 1994-Mar 22, 1994 (Box 174, Folder 21)
  - District 3 Meeting, Feb 25, 1995-Feb 28, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 22)
  - District 4 Area Meeting, May 29, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 23)
  - District 4 Conference, Nov 21, 1991-Nov 22, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 24)
  - District 4 Conference, Oct 19, 1993-Oct 20, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 25)
  - District 4 Conference, Mar 27, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 26)
  - District 4 Conference, Nov 16, 1995-Nov 17, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 27)
  - District 4 Legislative Meeting, Mar 20, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 28)